grabpcgames.com 2019-11-19

# Privacy Policy - GrabPCGames.com

At [ _ **www.GrabPCGames.com**_](https://www.grabpcgames.com/), the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by http://www.grabpcgames.com and how it is used. Please note that by visiting this website you must agree to the Terms and Conditions.

If you require any more information or have any questions about the privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by use of the [contact page](https://www.grabpcgames.com/contact/).

### **_Log Files:_**

Like many other Web sites, www.grabpcgames.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages and the number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

### _Access to Personal Information:_

Individuals can find out if  **GrabPCGames.com**  holds any personal information by making a ‘ _subject access request_ ‘ under the Data Protection Act 1998. If the site does hold information about you an admin can:

  * _Give you a description of it_
  * _Tell you why it is been held_
  * _Tell you who it could be disclosed to_
  * _Let you have a copy of the information in an intelligible form_

To make a request to  **GrabPCGames**  for any personal information that may be held, you need to put the request in writing addressing it to the address held by [ICANN](https://www.icann.org/) for the website (alternatively, this address can be given to you via email). If we do hold information about you, you can ask us to correct any mistakes.

If you agree, we will try to deal with your request informally, for example by providing you with the specific information you need via email.
